IBT0048
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 158 records
1948-1959
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0048
1.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material produced by Teamsters Local 158 of Milwaukee, WI dating from 1948-1959. Included are bank documents, cancelled checks, contracts and agreements, correspondence, a Local 158 newspaper, receipts and invoices, and other miscellaenous items.
Historical Note
Local 158 was a local Teamsters union located in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. The local members were employed in a variety of industries including dairy delivery, taxi services, industrial arts, and food processing, sales, warehousing, and distribution. The local ceased to exist in 1958 and the local's identifying number was later given to a Philadelphia local.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor unions -- Wisconsin -- History -- 20th century; Contracts; Labor unions; Labor; Collective labor agreements
- Bank Documents, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cancelled Checks, 1957 February 15 - 1959 March 12 (Oversize 2)
  General
  Box contains numerically-ordered cancelled checks dating from February 15, 1957 to March 12, 1959.
- Contracts and Agreements, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Honorable Withdrawal Cards, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Official Election Blanks, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Official Letterhead, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "Plan For Tomorrow" Newspaper, 1957 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Receipts and Invoices [1/3], 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Receipts and Invoices [2/3], 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Receipts and Invoices [3/3], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)